

#### Managed WP Hosting

Specialized website hosting for your WordPress website.

Daily Backups, automatic safe updates, and vulnerabilities automatically patched are all included in our Managed WP hosting.



#### NEW Website Builder

Build your website with the SiteJet website builder, No Coding Needed!

_60-day Free trial and a Free domain for the 1st year!  
No credit card required!_

Privacy Policy
==============

**Privacy Policy**
==================

Updated: 12/9/2021

_This document becomes effective for everyone on the date it was last updated._

The Privacy Policy is an agreement between Ness Web Solutions, LLC, of N9560 Buchert Lane, Watertown, WI 53904 here as known by “Host”, and the client who signed any contract for services, or who has purchased services from us, or is the employee any organization who has signed any contract, or has purchased services from us, here as known by “Client”. The “Host” will also be used to refer to its employees, agents, or representatives.

1. **GENERAL STATEMENT:** Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to https://nesswebsolutions.com, https://portal.nesswebsolutions.com and Ness Web Solutions, LLC and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Ness Web Solutions, LLC include https://nesswebsolutions.com and https://portal.nesswebsolutions.com. The Ness Web Solutions, LLC website is a e-commerce and client portal site. By using the Ness Web Solutions, LLC website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**2.1. COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA.** In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, Ness Web Solutions, LLC may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:

1. First Name
2. Last Name
3. Middle Initial
4. Mailing Address
5. Physical Address
6. Your preferred phone number
7. Business Office Phone Number
8. Employer
9. Job Title
10. Employer Address

If you purchase Ness Web Solutions, LLC’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction.

We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

If you upload images to the website or share images with us, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included.

**2.2. TWO-FACTOR & SECURITY QUESTIONS.** All Client Portal accounts are required to have two-factor authentication (also known as 2FA, 2-Factor Authentication & 2-Factor, Two-Step Login) enabled. Part of 2-factor authentication will ask a series of questions, of which you must answer 4 of. The information collected through 2-Factor Authentication & Security includes:

1. First Job
2. 6th grade school
3. City of first job
4. Maternal grandmothers maiden name
5. College graduation year
6. Cell Phone Number
7. Cell Phone Manufacturer
8. Cell Phone Model
9. Cell Phone Carrier

**3.1. SHARING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.** Ness Web Solutions, LLC will not sell, rent, or lease customer information.

Ness Web Solutions, LLC may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Ness Web Solutions, LLC, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Our 3rd Party Data Processor list can be found at: https://nesswebsolutions.com/policies/

**3.2****.** **PUBLIC INFORMATION.** Information that is considered public is:

1. First name of client
2. Last Name of client
3. Business name
4. Domain name
5. Host assigned Client ID number

**3.3****. PUBLIC INFORMATION FOR DOMAIN NAMES.** Domain names have certain information that must be public depending on what domain name is purchased. The following information is required to be public information for domain name registration, renewal, or up keep:

1. First Name of client
2. Last Name of client
3. Business name
4. Address including, street, city, zip code, and country
5. Phone number
6. Email address
7. Other technical aspects found based off domain name search

**3.4. EXCEPTIONS.** Any written waiver by the Client of these confidentiality obligations which allows the Host to disclose the Client’s confidential information to a third party will be limited to a single occurrence tied to the specific information disclosed to the specific third party, and the confidentiality clause will continue to be in effect for all other occurrences. Public information can be released to 3rd parties without notice from the Host.

Ness Web Solutions, LLC may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Ness Web Solutions, LLC or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Ness Web Solutions, LLC; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Ness Web Solutions, LLC, or the public.

4. **CONFIDENTIALITY** **OF HOST****.** The Host will not at any time or in any manner, either directly or indirectly, use for the personal benefit of the Host, or divulge, disclose, or communicate in any manner any information that is proprietary to the Client (e.g., trade secrets, know-how and confidential information). The Host will protect such information and treat it as strictly confidential. This provision shall continue to be effective after the termination of this Agreement. Upon termination of this Agreement, the Host will return to the Client all records, notes, documentation and other items that were used, created, or controlled by the Host during the term of this Agreement. The Client may seek and obtain injunctive relief against the release or threatened release of such information in addition to any other legal remedies which may be available.
5. **TRACKING USER BEHAVIOR.** Ness Web Solutions, LLC may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Ness Web Solutions, LLC, in order to determine what Ness Web Solutions, LLC services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Ness Web Solutions, LLC to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

We use Hotjar to track where users on the website click, therefor creating a heatmap of the website. By using this heatmap we can improve our website design and flow for better user experience.

6. **AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED INFORMATION.** Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Ness Web Solutions, LLC. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Ness Web Solutions, LLC website.
7. **USE OF COOKIES.** The Ness Web Solutions, LLC website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Ness Web Solutions, LLC pages, or register with Ness Web Solutions, LLC site or services, a cookie helps Ness Web Solutions, LLC to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Ness Web Solutions, LLC website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Ness Web Solutions, LLC features that you customized.

1. If you click accept on our cookie notice, we will set a cookie to remember your selection. This cookie contains no personal data, and is saved for 30 days.
2. If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
3. If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
4. When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed. We have payment cookies from Stripe to allow payment processing and payment method saving.
5. If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
6. If you visit our support center at help.nesswebsolutions.com you will have multiple session cookies to personalize your site visit, to log you in automatically, and to assist you with creating, replying, and viewing tickets.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you will not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Ness Web Solutions, LLC services or websites you visit.

If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

Please see our Cookie Policy at the link below for more information: https://nesswebsolutions.com/policies/cookie-policy-us/

8. **LINKS.** This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
9. **SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.** Ness Web Solutions, LLC secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Ness Web Solutions, LLC uses the following methods for this purpose:
10. SSL/TLS Certificate
11. net PCI Compliant website hosting & firewall
12. ElePass, for Client Password and Credential Management

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.

10. **CHILDREN UNDER THIRTEEN.** Ness Web Solutions, LLC does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
11. **E-MAIL COMMUNICATIONS.** From time to time, Ness Web Solutions, LLC may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our Services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from Ness Web Solutions, LLC or click on a link therein.

If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from Ness Web Solutions, LLC, you may opt out of such communications by clicking on the UNSUBSCRIBE button located at the bottom of the email.

12. **EXTERNAL DATA STORAGE SITES.** We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.
13. **HOW LONG WE RETAIN YOUR DATA.** For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see and edit their personal information at any time. Website administrators can also see and edit that information. We will retain all client data indefinitely for business purposes.
14. **WHAT RIGHTS YOU HAVE TO YOUR DATA.** If you have an account on this site, are a client, have been a client, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
15. **WHAT DATA BREACH PROCEDURES WE HAVE IN PLACE.** In the event of a data breach, we will contact all clients within 72 hours of knowing about the breach. We will work with our security vendors and website hosting provider find the breach, diagnose what information released, and fix the affected cause to ensure it cannot happen again. We will contact appropriate law enforcement and will work in full cooperation with them.

We have previously used MiniOrange for our 2 Factor Authentication system. Data is still securely stored with them until official business relations have ended.

16. **MINIORANGE PRIVACY POLICY:** miniOrange(“Us,” “We,” “Our,” “miniOrange,” or the “Company”) is committed to protecting the privacy of your information while you use our WordPress miniOrange Two Factor Plugin. We’ve crafted the policy below to help you understand how our plugin collects and uses personally identifiable information.

**16.1. DEFINITIONS.**

1. **miniOrange Two Factor Plugin**: This refers to Google Authenticator – Two **Factor Authentication (2FA) WordPress plugin.**
2. **Customer Support Services**: It involves screen sharing sessions, meetings and support by mail.
3. **miniOrange Servers**: This refers to miniOrange service which is stored on secure cloud service AWS. miniOrange Users data is also stored with AWS.
4. **Third Party**: This refers to customer using miniOrange services i.e. plugin to provide Two Factor verification to its users.
5. **Personal data**: This refers to information provided by you such as name, company name, address, phone number, email address, and any other information necessary.

**16.2. INTRODUCTION.** We protect your personal information using industry ­standard safeguards. We may share your information only with your consent or as required by law as detailed in this policy, and we will always let you know when we make significant changes to this Privacy Policy. Maintaining your trust is our top priority, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy:

We protect your personal information and will only provide it to third parties: (1) with your consent; (2) where it is necessary to carry out your instructions; (3) as reasonably necessary in order to provide our features and functionality to you; (4) when we reasonably believe it is required by law, subpoena or other legal process; or (5) as necessary to enforce our User Agreement or protect the rights, property, or safety of miniOrange, its Customers and Users, and the public.

**16.3. WHAT PERSONAL DATA DO WE COLLECT?.** miniOrange collects data provided by you while registering with miniOrange or through any other service while contacting miniOrange. We also collect data needed to provide miniOrange services. This data may contain different information as listed below:

1. When you register in the plugin, you provide us with information (including your name(optional), email address, phone number(optional), company name/website and password) that we use to offer you a personalized, relevant experience on miniOrange.
2. When User contacts our Customer Support, User’s personal data is shared which is necessary for us to provide support where we can assist you with the plugin configurations, setup or any other issues while using miniorange Two Factor Plugin. The Personal Data you provided is used for purposes like answering questions, improving the content of the website, customizing the content, and communicating with the customers about miniOrange’s Services, including specials and new features.
3. While using miniOrange Risk Based Authentication (RBA) services, device information is collected. The information collected for RBA is mentioned below under data used by the plugin.
4. When you contact us using our support form, we collect information that helps us categorize your question, respond to it, and, if applicable, investigate any breach of our User Agreement or this Privacy Policy. We also use this information to track potential problems and trends and customize our support responses to better serve you.
5. We do not collect email address from miniOrange production service for marketing use.

In the miniOrange Two Factor plugin, we collect the following information from users :

**Customer Details**: First name, last name, username, email, Questions and Answers of Security Questions, Phone Number, Company Name.  
**Device Information**: Location, Browser details, IP Address, Device Type, Time, Language, Useragent details, Device fingerprint

miniOrange only uses your data in order to provide you with the service and keeps this data available only to the user that has provided the information or the third parties that the user has agreed to grant access to.The data is also provided to respective Authenticator Application owner which is required for verification during login.

**16.4. HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION?.** miniOrange Two factor Plugin has various authentication methods and different methods require different information. Your Phone number and Email are used to send One Time Passcode. Your email is also used as a primary medium of contact only in case you need any help from us. Risk based Authentication uses information like device type, location, Ip address, time and other to identify the user and grant access based on the risk.

All data provided are stored with miniOrange which can be accessed through our site https://login.xecurify.com where the user’s account is created while using the miniOrange Two Factor Plugin.

**16.5. PERSONAL DATA PROCESSING DURATION.** Personal data will only be processed until we have a legitimate business. When we have no legitimate business, your data is stored securely until deletion. During this period, if you request for data stored with miniOrange, you would have to give sufficient evidence of identity before we can provide you with this information. You can request this by contacting us at [info@miniorange.com](mailto:info@miniorange.com). Same would apply if you request for deletion of the personal data.

1. **User consent**: End Users will be asked for consent if they agree to the terms and conditions of your website. If they deny consent, they will not be logged in and no data will be fetched.
2. **Encryption**: All data that is in transit because of miniOrange is encrypted in the miniOrange Two Factor plugin.

**16.6. WHAT ARE YOUR RIGHTS.**

1. **Right to be forgotten**: Information collected in stored in two places – WordPress Database and miniOrange Servers. Customer can delete end-user’s information if end-user requests.
2. **Right to object**: In certain situations, end user has the right to object to the data being processed in so far as such data have been collected for direct marketing purposes.
3. **Right to rectification**: You have a right for clarification of inaccurate personal data. And change the data by providing complete information.
4. **Right of access**: You have the right to obtain from us information concerning i.e. you have the right to request and get access to that personal data.

_The miniOrange Privacy Policy is Copyright of miniOrange, Inc. All Rights Reserved_

17. **CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT.** Ness Web Solutions, LLC reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.
18. **CONTACT INFORMATION.** Ness Web Solutions, LLC welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Ness Web Solutions, LLC has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Ness Web Solutions, LLC at:

**Business Address:**  
Ness Web Solutions, LLC  
584 Castro St  
#2009  
San Francisco, CA 94114-2512

Email Address: hello@nesswebsolutions.com  
Support Email Address: support@nesswebsolutions.com

Telephone number: 920-203-8145



#### (920) 203-8145



#### Hello@NessWebSolutions.com

© 2024 Ness Web Solutions, LLC

Manage Cookie Consent

To provide the best experiences, we use technologies like cookies to store and/or access device information. Consenting to these technologies will allow us to process data such as browsing behavior or unique IDs on this site. Not consenting or withdrawing consent, may adversely affect certain features and functions.

Functional  Functional Always active

The technical storage or access is strictly necessary for the legitimate purpose of enabling the use of a specific service explicitly requested by the subscriber or user, or for the sole purpose of carrying out the transmission of a communication over an electronic communications network.

Preferences  Preferences

The technical storage or access is necessary for the legitimate purpose of storing preferences that are not requested by the subscriber or user.

Statistics  Statistics

The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for statistical purposes. The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for anonymous statistical purposes. Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party, information stored or retrieved for this purpose alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

Marketing  Marketing

The technical storage or access is required to create user profiles to send advertising, or to track the user on a website or across several websites for similar marketing purposes.

Accept Deny View preferences Save preferences [View preferences](#)

Manage consent

Get in the Know!
----------------

Join our new sales & promotions mailing list!
---------------------------------------------

By joining our mailing list, you will receive emails about sales, promotions, and new products we are launching!

We won't spam you, we will only send you 1 email per month at most!

SUBSCRIBE!

You are now In The Know! about promotions & new product announcements!
----------------------------------------------------------------------

[Open toolbar Accessibility Tools](javascript:void(0); "Accessibility Tools")

Accessibility Tools
